simtel.net 2012-12-27

# Digital River is a leading provider of global e-commerce solutions.

Digital River values its relationship with you. These Privacy Statement Highlights summarize, at a high level, our full Privacy Statement about how Digital River collects, uses and discloses information about you through a commerce solution on which this Privacy Policy appears, which may be but is not limited to a website or a software application (each, a “Property”). These Highlights are intended for your convenience.  In the event of any conflict between the full Privacy Statement and these Highlights, the full Digital River Privacy Statement will govern.  For more information on any of these sections, please click the “Learn more” link to review the full Privacy Statement. 

How We Collect Information  
Learn More |   |  Storage, Use and Sharing of Information  
Learn More  
---|---|---  
  
  * When you, through this Property, request information about a product or service, purchase a product, or otherwise elect to participate in an activity, we may ask you to provide personal information.
  * If you contact us directly, such as through customer service, we may request information so we can respond to your question or comment and/or validate your identity.
  * We collect information sent to us through your web browser.
  * We may receive certain personal information about you from third parties where you have agreed to share such information with us. 

|   | 

  * We process your personal information on our servers, and/or through the servers of our subsidiaries and partners around the world.
  * We may use your personal information for the purposes set forth in the Privacy Statement, such as to process and complete your order if you are purchasing a product from us or communicate with you about other products or services.
  * We may share a copy of your personal information (excluding payment information) with our partner whose branding appears on an online store through which you provide us with personal information, and/or to the manufacturer or publisher of a product you purchase from us.
  * To the extent necessary, we may share your information with our third party contractors who assist us with providing services to you, such as but not limited to payment processing and fraud prevention, or in connection with this Property.
  * We will not share your personal information with our affiliates or unrelated 3rd parties for their own marketing purposes without your consent.

  |   |    
Cookies, Web Beacons and Web Technologies   
Learn more |   | Your Choices    
Learn more  
  
  * We use web technologies, such as persistent cookies, session cookies, JavaScript tags, Web beacons, and similar technologies, to collect information about your use of this Property that is typically not personally identifiable.
  * We may place web technologies on our Property directly or through our service providers, or on behalf of our partner whose branding appears or their service providers.
  * We and our partners use this information to provide you with a personalized online experience. We may use this information to improve the content and functionality of this Property and our products and services.

|   | 

  * You may indicate your choices as to whether you would like to receive further communications from us and/or our partners at the time and on the page where you provide your personal information.
  * You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. If you decide you no longer want to receive promotional messages from us by following any unsubscribe link in our emails or by contacting us. 
  * You can delete cookies at any time through your web browser.  You can also utilize a free third party service to make choices with respect to third party ad networks whose web technologies may appear on our Property.

  |   |    
Accessing or Correcting Your Personal Information    
Learn more |   | How to Contact Us  
Learn more  
  
  * If you would like to review, correct or dispute your personal information, please contact us.

|   | 

  * If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement or our privacy practices, or have privacy-related questions not answered online, please contact us.

  |   |    
  
**DIGITAL RIVER PRIVACY STATEMENT**  
**Last updated:   November 20, 2012**

BY USING THIS WEBSITE OR COMMERCE SOLUTION OR SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION TO DIGITAL RIVER THROUGH THIS WEBSITE OR COMMERCE SOLUTION, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE COLLECTION, USE, TRANSFER, AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT. 

This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 20, 2012. 

## Scope of this Privacy Statement

_In General._ This Privacy Statement applies to each commerce solution, which may be but is not limited to a website or a software application (each, a “Property”) operated by Digital River, Inc., 10380 Bren Road West, Minnetonka, Minnesota 55343, United States of America (“Digital River”) where this Privacy Statement can be accessed from a hyperlink on, or otherwise appears on, that Property.  If you are purchasing products through a Digital River subsidiary and not Digital River, Inc., please note that this Property is hosted and/or operated by Digital River under an agreement with the subsidiary of Digital River who is listed as the seller of products in the terms of sale on this Property.

Digital River respects the privacy of our customers, partners and suppliers of products or services and clients. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to provide you with information concerning how we collect personal information when you use this Property, and how we collect other information regarding your interaction with this Property without identifying you as an individual; how we use, handle and disclose collected information; and choices you may have about the ways we collect and use that information. Our goal in handling personal information provided to us is to comply with applicable data protection and privacy laws and to offer users of our Property notice, choice and consent regarding processing for direct marketing purposes, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement with regard to personal information.

“Personal information” means information that identifies you personally, either alone or in combination with other information available to us.  

_Supplemental Privacy Notices_.  This Privacy Statement may be supplemented or amended from time to time by additional “Privacy Notices” posted or appearing on this Property. Such Privacy Notice will provide supplemental information on how we collect and handle information specific to where that Privacy Notice appears, and is intended to be read together with this Privacy Statement. ****

_Third Party Privacy Policies or Statements_.  If you access a Property through which we offer products or services for sale, the Property may be co-branded with the name and branding of the organization whose product you are purchasing. If the privacy policy or statement of one of our partners also appears on this Property, this Privacy Statement will apply to our use of any information collected by us, and the privacy policy or statement of our partner will apply to any such information provided to that partner as contemplated by this Privacy Statement and any supplemental Privacy Notices.

## Changes to this Privacy Statement

We may occasionally update this Privacy Statement.  These updates may reflect, among other things, changes in applicable laws, rules or regulations, changes in our data collection practices, and/or changes to our business or services.  Changes to our Privacy Statement will become effective 30 days after posting and will only apply to your personal information we hold if you use the site after the revised statement becomes effective. If revisions to the Privacy Statement materially affect how we may use Personal Information collected from you prior to the date of the revised statement, then we will request that you opt-in to the revised Privacy Statement. We will post an updated version of this Privacy Statement on the Property with a revised effective date, to let you know that we updated the Privacy Statement.

## Collection of Information

We collect personal information you provide when you use this Property. This may include, but is not limited to, the following situations: where you are providing information when you request information about, or use, a product or service available through this Property, or information you provide when you purchase a product or service through this Property; where you are entering a contest or a promotion, ordering a newsletter or utilizing other informational tools; and where you are submitting an order or purchasing, downloading and/or registering products and/or signing up for additional services.

The information we collect may include, but is not limited to, your name, e-mail address, IP address, billing and/or shipping address, phone number, payment account information, and other information about you submitted to verify who you are or to prevent fraud.  If you call our customer service, we may collect personal information you knowingly and voluntarily provide through your contact with our customer service representatives. 

We furthermore collect information that is sent to us by your web browser, which may include without limitation information that does not identify you personally (such as the date and time of your visit, information about your web browser, etc.). The information we receive in such manner depends on the settings on your web browser. If you have created a user identity on one of your visits to this Property, we may link the information provided by your browser to information that identifies you personally and use it for the purposes described below. Please review the settings of your web browser if you want to learn what information your browser can send or how to change your browser settings.

We may also receive certain personal information about you from third parties where you have agreed to share such information with us, such as through your use of a social network authentication to sign in to this Property.

## Cookies and Web Beacons, JavaScript tags, and Other Web Technologies

We collect information that is typically not personally identifiable through the use of web technologies, including without limitation “session cookies,” “persistent cookies,” “web beacons” (also referred to as “tracking pixels,” “pixel tags,” or “action tags”), and “JavaScript tags.” As the Internet evolves, we may implement and use different types of technologies for this purpose. ****

We may place web technologies on this site directly or through our third party providers, and may place web technologies on behalf of the partner whose branding appears on this Property or its service providers and allow that partner to utilize the data collected.  This information is used to enhance your use and experience with this Property, for marketing analysis, and for quality improvement purposes.  They also help us identify your IP address.  The information collected by web technologies does not identify you personally. However, if you have created a user identity on one of your visits to this Property, for example, by making a purchase, we may link the information we collect using web technologies to the information that identifies you personally.

_Cookies_.  When you visit or use this Property, your computer may receive one or more “cookies” in order to help personalize and support your use of this Property, our services, and/or the services of our partners.  A “cookie” is a small text file that is transferred to a web browser by a web server, and can be read by a web server in the same domain at a later time.  If you do not wish to receive cookies or wish to manage when you accept cookies in general, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. We provide more information on this in the “Your Choices” section, below. Although you are not required to accept our cookies, if you set your browser to reject cookies, you may not be able to use all of the features and functionality of this Property. Cookies allow us to customize information that is presented to you through your use of a Property we host and/or operate (such as to display personalized content and targeted advertising to you on your future visits to that Property), and to save time by storing information so you do not need to re-enter it during a later use of a Property. In general, cookies do not identify you personally. We may use a combination of “session cookies” and “persistent cookies” on this Property, further described below.

_Session Cookies._ A “session cookie” is a temporary cookie that expires when you close your browser. A session cookie assigns a randomly-generated, unique identification number to your computer when you access this Property. Assigning your computer a number facilitates the proper functioning of the features of our Property by permitting us to maintain a persistent “state” for your session, such as maintaining the contents of your shopping cart during checkout. We also use session cookies to collect anonymous information (i.e., information that does not identify you personally) about the ways visitors use this Property – which pages they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page. We analyze this information (known as “click-stream information”) to better understand our visitors’ interests and needs and to improve the content and functionality of this Property.

_Persistent Cookies._ Unlike a session cookie, a “persistent cookie” does not expire when you close your browser. It stays on your computer until the expiration date set in the cookie (for example, at the end of a calendar month) or until you delete it.  Persistent cookies can be used to “tag” your computer so that the next time you visit (or someone using your computer visits), our server will recognize you, not by name, but by the “tag” on your computer. This will enable us to provide you with a personalized experience even if we do not know who you are. It will also allow us to collect more accurate information about the ways people use this Property, for example, how people use this Property on their first visit and how often they return.  Using persistent cookies permits us to provide you with a more personalized shopping experience and, in some cases, may save you the trouble of re-entering information already in our database.

_Web Beacons.   _When you visit or use this Property, your computer may receive one or more “web beacons” in order to assist us with delivering cookies on this Property, to collect anonymous information about the use of this Property by our visitors, and to deliver customized or targeted content to you on this Property and through our partners.  Web beacons (also referred to as “tracking pixels,” “1x1 gifs,” “single-pixel gifs,” “pixel tags,” or “action tags”) are graphic images, usually no larger than a 1x1 pixel, placed at various locations on this Property. They also help us identify browser types, search terms that bring visitors to our Property, and the domain names of websites that refer traffic to us. We also utilize web beacons to provide us with more information on any emails we send out.  In particular, a web beacon in an email communication will send us information to let us know that you have received, opened, or acted upon an e-mail you have chosen to receive from us. ****

_JavaScript Tags.   _This Property may include one or more JavaScript tags which are used by us to collect anonymous information about the use of this Property by our visitors, and to deliver customized or targeted content to you on this Property and through our partners.  We may use JavaScript tags to anonymously track how visitors interact with our Properties, including where they came from and the manner in which they use our Properties.

## Storage, Use and Sharing of Information

Your personal information provided to us will be processed on our computer servers.  In some cases (where it is necessary to do so in order to fulfill our contractual obligations to you) such information may also be transmitted or made available to (i) third-parties providing services to Digital River or (ii) product manufacturers, licensors and/or or suppliers, located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), the United States of America or another territory outside the EEA.

_Our Use of Personal Information.   _We may use personal information collected by us for the following purposes: 

to contact you if you have requested information or communication from us;

  * to determine the country in which you are located for compliance purposes (including without limitation export compliance) and for security, anti-piracy, and fraud prevention purposes;
  * to help verify that existing personal information about you in our possession is accurate and complete;
  * to provide you with product updates and upgrades, special offers, pricing information, newsletters, and other information, either on our own behalf or in some cases on behalf of a partner or client acting as their agent, where you have consented to receive it;
  * to undertake any other promotional activities where you have consented to such promotional activities;
  * in connection with keys, access codes or other information as may be required to permit you to access the websites or services of our partners to receive products, updates or services;
  * for the purposes identified in a specific Supplemental Privacy Notice posted on the page or area of this Property where you provided that information;
  * to verify compliance with applicable laws, rules and regulations;
  * if you visit this Property for the purposes of conducting a purchase transaction: 
    * to take, verify, process or deliver your order, process or obtain payment, verify your tax or tax exempt status, contest chargebacks, determine your eligibility for a line of credit, or notify you of the status of your order;
    * for fraud and piracy prevention purposes;
    * to provide you, to the extent permitted by law, with a personalized shopping experience;
    * to register your purchase with the manufacturer or service provider for warranty, technical support or similar purposes;
    * to provide notice of your purchase to the provider of an online service for which you purchase a service use right from us, for example, in order for the service provider to enable your access to the service; 
    * to establish an account for future purchases by you if you have consented to the creation of an account;
    * to facilitate the renewal of subscriptions for products or services; and
    * to provide you with effective customer service (which may to the extent and in a manner permitted by applicable law, include contacting visitors who commence but do not complete a checkout process to follow up on the incomplete session or to see if there was a problem with their use of this Property), and/or technical support.

We keep your personal information only as long as we need it for the purposes for which it was originally collected (or to which you have subsequently consented), for other legitimate purposes (such as regulatory compliance), and as permitted or required by applicable law. We will observe applicable law and take reasonable steps to ensure any person or entity receiving personal information for the purposes described above, are obligated to protect and keep secure the personal information on your behalf. ****

_Our Use of Anonymous Information.   _We may use anonymous information collected by us:

  * to personalize and support your use of this Property, our services, and/or the services of our partners; 
  * to improve this Property, the customer experience, our advertising systems, and our products and services;
  * for fraud prevention purposes, such as device fingerprinting;
  * to identify actions or transactions as originating through an affiliate marketing or referral program;
  * to deliver targeted advertisements on this Property and other websites and/or commerce solutions;
  * to provide reporting to our current and prospective partners and service providers; and
  * for other historical, statistical or research and analysis purposes.

In addition, we may “de-identify” personal information by removing any information that identifies you specifically, and use the rest for the purposes set forth above. ****

_Our Partners._ When we make products available for sale through a Property, we are doing so as an independent e-commerce reseller of, or service provider for, the partner whose name and/or logo appears on the particular Property. In connection with your purchase of a product or service through an online store we operate that is co-branded with our partner’s branding, we will provide certain of the personal information and/or anonymous information you provide in connection with your purchase to that partner for reporting purposes, to allow our partner or its service provider to register your purchase, to enable your access to products or services provided by our partner or its suppliers, to facilitate warranty, technical support or after-sales service, to allow our partner or its subcontractor to send communications to you if you have consented to receive them, to allow our partner or its service provider to provide services in connection with this Property such as customer support or single sign-on functionality on this Property and our partner’s website, or for similar purposes in order to fulfill obligations to you. We may also provide certain of the personal information you provide in connection with your purchase to the publisher or manufacturer of a product you purchase, or operator of a service for which you purchase a service use right from us, if different than the partner whose name and/or logo appears on this Property.  The privacy policy of our partner, and of the publisher, manufacturer or operator of the product or service you purchase, will govern how that party uses and protects any of your personal information that we provide to them.

_Our Service Providers_. We utilize other companies, including but not limited to our corporate affiliates, to provide joint services or certain services to us or on our behalf and help us to operate our business. For example, to the extent permitted by applicable law we may use our corporate affiliates and/or other companies to host or maintain this Property, to process credit card payments, to provide fraud screening and/or detection services, to perform data integrity checks, to offer you a line of credit, to provide optimization services, to fulfill your order, for payment collection, to deliver advertisements on this Property and third party websites and/or commerce solutions, to send mail or e-mail, and/or to provide customer service. We may share your information with our service providers in connection with their provision of services to us.  These companies are required by contract to use any information we share with them only to perform services to us or on our behalf and to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. We may also allow these companies to utilize anonymous information, and to utilize aggregated personal information on an anonymous basis (i.e., where the aggregated data cannot identify you personally), for their business purposes.  We will not share your personal information with our affiliates or unrelated third parties to use for their own marketing purposes without your consent. ****

_To Comply With Legal Requirements, Cooperate With Law Enforcement, Prevent Fraud and Other Crimes, and Protect Legal Rights, Property, You and Others_. To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may disclose the personal information we collect on this Property without notifying you when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law or a regulatory requirement; to comply with governmental, administrative or judicial process, requirement or order, such as a subpoena or court order; to cooperate with law enforcement or other governmental investigations (without necessarily requiring the law enforcement or government agency requesting the information to formally serve us with a subpoena); to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce a contract; to protect the legal rights, property or safety of Digital River, its corporate affiliates, and their respective employees, clients and partners and agents, other users or the public in general; or to protect your vital interests if determined necessary by us. In addition, we may review our server logs for security purposes, such as detecting intrusions into our network. If we suspect criminal activity, we may share our server logs – which contain visitors’ IP addresses – with the appropriate investigative authorities who may use that information to trace and identify individuals. We also reserve the right to report to appropriate law enforcement or government agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe are or may be in violation of applicable laws, rules or regulations without providing notice to you.

_In Connection With Corporate Events_. If one of our corporate affiliates or a third party has acquired our business, specific assets or the business of one of our operating divisions through which you have provided information to us, for example, as the result of a sale, merger, reorganization, insolvency, dissolution or liquidation, your personal information will become owned by that company. In that event, the acquiring company’s use of your personal information will still be subject to this Privacy Statement, any applicable Supplemental Privacy Notices, and the privacy preferences you have expressed to us.

## Your Choices

Digital River respects your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use and disclose information about you. We generally ask you to indicate your choices at the time and on the page where you provide your personal information.

When you provide personal information, we may offer you a choice as to whether you would like to receive further communications from us and/or from our partners, such as communications related to updates, upgrades, special offers and pricing. You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. If you decide you no longer want to receive promotional messages from us, you may let us know by e-mailing us at [remove@digitalriver.com](mailto:remove@digitalriver.com) or by following any unsubscribe link in our e-mails; please specify which consent you are revoking in your e-mail to us. Please note, however, if you give us permission to add your contact information to our Partner’s mailing list and later withdraw your permission, you will have to contact our Partner (or use the “opt-out” provided in the e-mails our Partner sends you) to have your name removed from our Partner’s mailing lists.

If you accept a session or persistent cookie, you can delete it at any time through your web browser (e.g., as soon as you leave our Property).  If you do not wish to receive cookies or wish to manage when you accept cookies in general, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. Although you are not required to accept our cookies, if you set your browser to reject cookies, you may not be able to use all of the features and functionality of this Property.

We and our partners use third party service providers in connection with this Property and our business, which may include but are not limited to (a) Google Analytics and Omniture to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this Property, and (b) ClickTale to gather user metrics and usage data. These service providers may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Property or to a website, your interaction with our Property or that website, and the products and services offered by us, our partners and our suppliers through the use of cookies, pixel tags, JavaScript code or other web technologies.  We and our partners may use this anonymous information to provide targeted advertisements to you for goods and services, for marketing analysis, and for quality improvement purposes. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used, please visit [www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).  You may view a list of third party service providers who collect anonymous information, and/or opt-out of such collection of anonymous information about you, by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. **  **If you would like to opt-out of tracking of your anonymous information through ClickTale, please visit <http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html>. If you opt out of having your information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tools, your existing display advertising cookie(s) will be deleted and new cookie will attempt to be placed that instructs service providers not to track your future activities when that cookie is detected (a “no-track” cookie).  If your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit our opt-out page, a “no-track” cookie cannot be set on your computer.  Also, if you subsequently erase “no-track” cookies, use a different computer or change web browsers, you will need to opt-out again. 

## Security of Information

We are committed to keeping personal information secure. We have implemented physical, technical and administrative safeguards reasonably designed to protect your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. When we collect or transmit sensitive information such as a financial account number, we use industry standard methods to protect that information. It is important that you understand, however, that no commerce solution, website, database or system is completely secure or “hacker proof.” You are also responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse, for example, by protecting your password. Different countries have different privacy laws and requirements. Please know, however, that no matter where your personal information is collected, used, transferred or stored, if it was collected through this Property, it will be protected by us in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Statement, any Supplemental Privacy Notices that apply to you, and applicable laws, rules and regulations. 

## Accessing and Correcting Your Personal Information

We strive to maintain the accuracy and integrity of the personal information in our databases and to keep that information up-to-date. We provide ways for you to access your personal information as required by applicable law, so that you can correct inaccuracies or update your personal information.

If you would like to review, correct or challenge your personal information, please contact us by postal mail addressed to us, ATTN: Privacy Department, at 10380 Bren Road West, Minnetonka, Minnesota 55343, United States of America or by e-mail at [privacy@digitalriver.com](mailto:privacy@digitalriver.com). You may write to us in your own language.

If you contact us we may, for your protection, ask you for additional information to verify your identity. In most cases, we will provide the access you request and correct or delete any inaccurate personal information you discover. We reserve the right, however, to limit or deny your request to the extent permitted by applicable law if the disclosure may lead to a breach of applicable law and regulation, e.g. in case of any legal obligation to retain certain data, or if you have failed to provide sufficient evidence to verify your identity.

## Links to Third Party websites

This Property is not directed at nor targeted to children. If you have not reached the age of majority or are not able to enter into legally binding agreements in your country, you may not use this Property unless supervised by an adult.  Our goal is to comply with applicable laws and regulations relating to collection and use of information from children as such term is defined by applicable laws. If you believe that we have received information from a child or other person protected under such laws, please notify us immediately by postal mail addressed to Digital River’s Privacy Department, 10380 Bren Road West, Minnetonka, Minnesota 55343, United States of America or by e-mail at [privacy@digitalriver.com](mailto:privacy@digitalriver.com), and we will take reasonable steps to remove that information from our databases.

## Children's privacy

This Property is not directed at nor targeted to children. If you have not reached the age of majority or are not able to enter into legally binding agreements in your country, you may not use this Property unless supervised by an adult.  Our goal is to comply with applicable laws and regulations relating to collection and use of information from children as such term is defined by applicable laws. If you believe that we have received information from a child or other person protected under such laws, please notify us immediately by postal mail addressed to Digital River’s Privacy Department, 10380 Bren Road West, Minnetonka, Minnesota 55343, United States of America or by e-mail at [privacy@digitalriver.com](mailto:privacy@digitalriver.com), and we will take reasonable steps to remove that information from our databases.

## How to Contact Us

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement or our privacy practices, or have privacy-related questions not answered online, you may contact us by any of the following means:

  * _By Mail:_ You may contact us by postal mail addressed to Digital River, Inc., ATTN: Privacy Department, 10380 Bren Road West, Minnetonka, Minnesota 55343, United States of America.
  * _By Email:_ You may contact us by e-mail at [privacy@digitalriver.com](mailto:privacy@digitalriver.com).  Please specify “Global Privacy Question” in the subject line to help us to expedite our review of your e-mail.

You may write to us in your own language.

## Country Specific Notices

_Countries in the European Economic Area (“EEA”)_  
Digital River Ireland Ltd, Unit 153, Shannon Free Zone West, Shannon, Co. Clare, Ireland, and Digital River International Sarl, 9b, Boulevard du Prince Henri, L-1724 Luxembourg, Luxembourg, are both subsidiaries of Digital River, Inc., a U.S. corporation with offices at 10380 Bren Road West, Minnetonka, Minnesota 55343, United States of America.  If you are located in the EEA, by using this Property you consent to the transfer of your personal data to Digital River, Inc.’s servers in the United States and the processing of your personal data in the United States for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Statement, and acknowledge that your personal data may be transmitted by us to other Digital River companies for the purposes set out in this Privacy Statement and for company group administration purposes. This will involve a transfer of your personal data to Digital River Inc. in the United States of America.

* * *

### DMCA Notice

Digital River, Inc. and its affiliated companies respect the intellectual property of others and expect the users of our services to do the same. 

**Procedure for Making Copyright Infringement Claims:**  
If you believe that your copyrighted work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement and is accessible on this site or through this service, you may notify our copyright agent, as set forth in the Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998 (DMCA). For your complaint to be valid under the DMCA, you must provide the following information when providing notice of the claimed copyright infringement: 

  * A physical or electronic signature of the copyright owner(s) or a person authorized to act on his/her behalf. 
  * Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed. 
  * Identification of the material that is alleged to be infringing.
  * The contact information of the person filing the Notice. 
  * A statement from the person filing the Notice that they have a good faith belief that the material is infringing. 
  * A statement explaining that a) the provided information in the Notice is accurate, b) under penalty of perjury, the person filing the Notice is the copyright owner or that he/she is authorized to act on behalf of the copyright owner. 

The above information must be submitted as a written notification to the following Designated Agent:  
**Service Provider(s):** Digital River, Inc., www.regnow.com, www.regsoft.com, www.digibuy.com, www.ccnow.com, www.freemerchant.com, www.safeshopper.com, www.mainstreet-stores.com, www.simtel.com, www.digitalriver.com, www.regsoft.net, www.topdownloads.com 

**Name of Agent Designated to Receive Notification of Claimed Infringement: Jackie Romano**   
**Address of Designated Agent:** 9625 West 76th Street, Eden Prairie, MN 55344  
**Attn:** DMCA Office   
**Telephone Number of Designated Agent:** (952) 253-1234   
**Facsimile Number of Designated Agent:** (952) 674-4444 - Attention: DMCA Office   
**Email Address of Designated Agent:** [**dmca@digitalriver.com**](mailto:dmca@digitalriver.com)

WE CAUTION YOU THAT UNDER FEDERAL LAW, IF YOU KNOWINGLY MISREPRESENT THAT ONLINE MATERIAL IS INFRINGING, YOU MAY BE SUBJECT TO HEAVY CIVIL PENALTIES. THESE INCLUDE MONETARY DAMAGES, COURT COSTS, AND ATTORNEYS’ FEES INCURRED BY US, BY ANY COPYRIGHT OWNER, OR BY ANY COPYRIGHT OWNER’S LICENSEE THAT IS INJURED AS A RESULT OF OUR RELYING UPON YOUR MISREPRESENTATION. YOU MAY ALSO BE SUBJECT TO CRIMINAL PROSECUTION FOR PERJURY. 

This information should not be construed as legal advice, for further details on the information required for valid DMCA notifications, see 17 U.S.C. 512(c)(3). 

NOTE: This information is provided exclusively for notifying the service providers referenced above that your copyrighted material(s) might have been infringed. All other inquiries, including technical requests, reports of email abuse and third-party reports of piracy, will not receive a response through this process. 

* * *

### Anti-Piracy Policy:

All Digital River, Inc. services may be used for lawful purposes only. Transmission, storage, or presentation of any information, data or material in violation of any United States Federal, State or City law is prohibited. This includes, but is not limited to: copyrighted material, material we judge to be inappropriate, threatening, obscene, or of adult content. Or, material protected by trade secret and other statute. For the purposes of this document, it is focused on anti-piracy. 

Piracy of any software or products is prohibited on all Digital River sites. This includes sites that sell the product directly or link to piracy sites/products elsewhere. 

**What is Piracy?**

  1. The illegal copying and distribution of copyrighted or patented material.
  2. The use of a product beyond the terms of its license. 
  3. Any attempt to reproduce the product illegally and make the packaging look like the original, but is counterfeit. 
  4. Any site whose revenue is gained all or in part from its piracy products. 
  5. Revenue-generating hyperlinks to sites that violate any part of descriptions 1-4. 

Digital River, Inc. reserves the right to decide what it considers “piracy.”  
Digital River, Inc. reserves the right to review or revise this policy at any time without notice. 

* * *

### Vendor Code of Conduct: 

Digital River, Inc., as well as all of its subsidiaries and divisions, (hereinafter "Digital River") require that all of our vendors abide by a code of ethics and performance even if the code is not part of a written contract. Digital River's continuing use of a vendor will be contingent on the vendor's satisfactory compliance with this Code. This Code applies equally if the customer is Digital River or a third party. The term Vendor includes suppliers of any product or service, including software contractors and sub-contractors. 

**Results** \- Vendor will strive to finish tasks efficiently in the allotted time and within the allotted budget. 

**Attitude** \- Vendor will strive to work smoothly with other team members, and help integrate their efforts into the project as a whole. Vendor will maintain a good attitude while waiting for the customer to pay for invoices, for example, and will be easy to do business. 

**Value** \- Vendor will strive to deliver work product that is free of defects, adheres to standards, is of a professional quality, and works as expected and agreed upon. 

**Planning** \- Vendor will plan ahead and solve the business problem first, design before developing, and test before deploying. Vendor will document the work product so others can take over the effort should circumstances require. 

**Communication** \- Vendor will communicate their status in a timely and regular way on the work product even if it might negatively affect its position. Vendor will notify the relevant parties when a project is outside of its area of expertise or skill level, or if a reasonable person who is fully aware of the situation would understand that Vendor needs help to get back on track. 

**Integrity** \- Vendor will not knowingly misrepresent facts. Vendor will not knowingly use unlicensed software. Vendor will fully divulge all conflicts of interest prior to contract, or as soon as is reasonably possible after discovery. Vendor will abide by the terms of its contracts and the law. Vendor will not divulge (unless required by law) or make use of confidential or proprietary information belonging to others. Vendor will take care to invoice only for hours actually worked or milestones fully attained. 

**Commitment** \- Vendor will demonstrate loyalty to Digital River and not interfere in the relationship of Digital River and any Digital River customer. Vendor will not do anything to disparage the reputation of either himself /herself, Digital River, nor any Digital River customer. 

* * *

### Illicit and Inappropriate Content Policy: 

All Digital River, Inc. services may be used for lawful purposes only. Transmission, storage, or presentation of any information, data or material in violation of any United States Federal, State or City law is prohibited. This includes, but is not limited to: copyrighted material, material we judge to be inappropriate, threatening, obscene, or unlawful. Or, material protected by trade secret and other statute. For the purposes of this document, it is focused on illicit and inappropriate content. 

The sale of illicit and inappropriate products is prohibited on all Digital River sites. This includes sites that may sell illicit and inappropriate products directly or link to illicit and inappropriate products elsewhere. This also includes money laundering as it is unlawful and prohibited by Digital River, Inc. Any site that directly or indirectly uses any product or links to any product for the purpose of laundering money is strictly prohibited.  
Because the Internet is a global communication tool, it is difficult to dictate what is considered "inappropriate content." It is not our function to discriminate against those who choose to utilize inappropriate content or products. However, Digital River, Inc. has chosen to enforce its “no illicit and inappropriate sites/products” policy. 

**What is Illicit or Inappropriate Content/products?**

  1. Any product that is illegal or unlawful (including but not limited to: money laundering.)  
  2. Any product that may be considered inappropriate (including but not limited to: drugs, alcohol, tobacco, firearms and explosives.) 
  3. Any site whose revenue is gained all or in part from its illicit and inappropriate products. 
  4. Revenue-generating hyperlinks to sites that violate any part of descriptions 1-3. 

Digital River, Inc. reserves the right to decide what it considers "inappropriate content" or "inappropriate products".   
Digital River, Inc. reserves the right to review or revise this policy at any time without notice. 

* * *

### Adult Content Policy:

All Digital River, Inc. services may be used for lawful purposes only. Transmission, storage, or presentation of any information, data or material in violation of any United States Federal, State or City law is prohibited. This includes, but is not limited to: copyrighted material, material we judge to be inappropriate, threatening, obscene, or of adult content. Or, material protected by trade secret and other statute. For the purposes of this document, it is focused on adult content.

Adult content **,** pornography and sex-related merchandising are prohibited on all Digital River sites. This includes sites that may infer sexual content or link to adult content elsewhere.   
Because the Internet is a global communication tool, it is difficult to dictate what is considered "adult content." It is not our function to discriminate against those who choose to utilize adult content or adult related material. However, Digital River, Inc. has chosen to enforce its “no adult sites/products” policy. 

**What is Adult Content?**

  1. Sexually explicit pictures, writing, or other material/products whose primary purpose is to cause sexual arousal. 
  2. Sexually explicit pictures, writing or any material/products that involves children (anyone under the age of 18) is strictly prohibited. 
  3. Photos, videos or animated depiction showing nudity in women or men for non-scientific or non-artistic purposes. 
  4. Any site whose revenue is gained all or in part from its adult content or products. 
  5. Revenue-generating hyperlinks to sites that violate any part of descriptions 1-4.

Digital River, Inc. reserves the right to decide what it considers "adult content", "adult material", "sexually explicit", or "sexually related".  
Digital River, Inc. reserves the right to review or revise this policy at any time without notice. 

* * *

### Gambling Policy:

All Digital River, Inc. services may be used for lawful purposes only. Transmission, storage, or presentation of any information, data or material in violation of any United States Federal, State or City law is prohibited. This includes, but is not limited to: copyrighted material, material we judge to be inappropriate, threatening, obscene, or unlawful. Or, material protected by trade secret and other statute. For the purposes of this document, it is focused on gambling. 

Gambling and gambling sites, where money is exchanged, are prohibited. Online video games that involve gambling, i.e.: blackjack, poker, etc are allowed provided there is no money or exchange of money involved and provided they do not violate any of Digital River’s other policies (including, but not limited to, adult content, illicit content or piracy.) 

Because the Internet is a global communication tool, it is difficult to dictate what is considered "gambling." It is not our function to discriminate against those who choose to utilize gambling or its products. However, Digital River, Inc. has chosen to enforce its “no gambling” policy. 

**What is Gambling?**

  1. Any product/site where money is exchanged or utilized for gambling. 
  2. Any product/site that promotes online casinos/betting. 
  3. Any product/site that promotes sports bets. 
  4. Any product/site that promotes the lottery. 
  5. Any site whose revenue is gained all or in part from its gambling or gambling products. 
  6. Revenue-generating hyperlinks to sites that violate any part of descriptions 1-4. 

Digital River, Inc. reserves the right to decide what it considers "gambling".   
Digital River, Inc. reserves the right to review or revise this policy at any time without notice.
